(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-12T21:17:18.996948",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
尾丸ポルカ 生誕祭2026 新曲のお披露目あり！ Glitter Love
[Omaru Polka Birthday Celebration 2026 - Glitter Love]
遥か天空 響いている
Echoing in the distant sky,
祈りは
my prayers...
奇跡に
become miracles.
真夜中の蒼に溶けて
Dissolving into the blue midnight,
流れてく涙の粒
the flowing teardrops.
迷いなく包み込む
Enveloping without hesitation,
温もりに出出会った
I encountered warmth.
真っ白な雪のように
Like pure white snow,
どこまでも素直なコトバ
your endlessly honest words
鉄の羽根纏った
set me in motion as I wrapped
僕を動かしていく
my steel wings around me.
傷つくたびに
Every time I get hurt,
優しくなれる
I can become kinder.
君のその笑顔だけ
I want to protect only your smile
守り抜きたい
until the very end,
願いはひとつ
I have only one wish.
時空を越え刻まれた
Engraved across time and space
悲しみの記憶
are memories of sorrow.
まっすぐに受け止める
Accepting them head-on,
君は光の女神
you are an angel of light.
あの日胸に灯った
The eternal flame
永遠の炎を
lit in my heart that day
深い闇解き放って
releases the deep darkness
自由のトビラ開いてく
and opens the door to freedom.
強く果てない未来へ
Toward a strong and endless future.
冷たい緑の月に
Reflected on the cold green moon
映し出すココロの夜
is the shadow of my heart.
寂しげにつぶやいた
I whispered lonely,
『君のそばにいたい』
"I want to be by your side."
真実と向き合うこと
The courage you gave me
教えてくれた勇気は
to face the truth
僕を駆け巡って
surges through me
夢に目覚めていく
and awakens me to my dream.
触れ合う気持ち
Our touching feelings,
離れないように
so they won't part,
しっかりと抱きしめて
hold them tight,
確かな想い貫いてゆく
and push through with unwavering feelings.
銀の海に隠した
Hidden in the silver sea
空白のページ
is a blank page.
君だけが知っている
Show me the "truth"
『本当』を僕に見せて
that only you know.
吹き荒れる切なさに
An oath born from
生まれゆく誓い
the raging heartbreak.
もう何も怖くはないよ
I am no longer afraid of anything,
結んだ視線そらさずに
without turning away our locked gaze,
大切な『今』始める
we begin this precious "now."
君が君でいられる場所
A place where you can be yourself,
悪夢にさらわれぬように
so you won't be taken by nightmares,
消えない雨の苦しみも
even the pain of endless rain,
鍵を壊して
break the lock
ぶつけてよ
and let it out to me,
隣にいるから
because I'm by your side,
すべてを信じて
believe in everything.
時空を越え刻まれた
Engraved across time and space
悲しみの記憶
are memories of sorrow.
まっすぐに受け止める
Accepting them head-on,
君は光の女神
you are an angel of light.
あの日胸に灯った
The eternal flame
永遠の炎を
lit in my heart that day,
深い闇
releasing the deep darkness...
解放って
...release it,
自由の扉 開いてく
opening the doors of freedom,
強く果てない未来へ
towards a strong and endless future!
そう きっと ここから 始まる
Yes, it definitely starts right here!
お待たせ、みんな！
Thanks for waiting, everyone!
今年もポルカの生誕祭が始まったー！
Polka's Birthday Concert is starting again this year!
タイトルはかっこいい「GLITTER LOVE」！ということで
The title is cool: "GLITTER LOVE"! And with that...
ハッシュタグはこちら！ #尾丸ポルカ生誕祭2026 でいっぱい、いっぱい呟いてねー！
Here's the hashtag! Please tweet lots using #尾丸ポルカ生誕祭2026!
はーい！
All right!
いやぁ、今回のテーマはまず、愛と勇気と戦う女の子になってます！
Well, the theme this time is about fighting girls with love and courage!
そして、見てくださいこのステージ！
And check out this stage!
はー！すごい広い！
Woah! It's super wide!
おー！なんとですね、広いんですけれど、まずスクリーンが超デカイ！
Woah! Not only is it wide, but the screen is huge!
大迫力！
It's so impactful!
なんとなんかいつもの3倍くらい頑張りました！
We put in like three times the effort compared to usual!
いや、頑張ってもらいました！ありがとうございます！
Well, everyone worked hard for it! Thank you so much!
というわけでですね、ここからゲストの方々が沢山いらっしゃいます！
So then, from here on, we have lots of guests joining us!
もうホロメンだけなら多分、尾丸ポルカ史上最多のゲスト数だと思っております！
Just counting Hololive members, I think it's the largest number of guests in Polka's history!
それをね、これからノンストップでお送りするので楽しんでいってください！
We'll be bringing you non-stop performances, so please enjoy!
というわけで、行くぞー！
Here we go!
遺伝子レベルの
On a genetic level,
インディペンデンス
Independence.
絶望も希望も
Embrace both despair and hope,
抱いて抗え
and fight back!
命尽きるまで
Until life runs out!
星天ギャラクシィクロス
[Song: Seiten Galaxy Cross]
光と吐息のキス
A kiss of light and sighs,
濃密な虹のバースデイ
a dense rainbow birthday.
どんな美しい日々も
No matter how beautiful the days are,
何か生まれ 何かが死ぬ
something is born and something dies.
せめて歌おう
At least let's sing,
I love you... 世界が酷い地獄だとしても
"I love you..." even if the world is a terrible hell.
せめて伝えよう
At least let's convey,
I love you... 解放の時は来た
"I love you..." the time for release has come.
星降る天へと
Into the star-filled heavens,
響きとべ Everybody song
soar and echo, everybody's song!
Stardust!
そう奇跡は待つものじゃなくて
Yes, miracles aren't something to wait for,
その手で作るものと誇れ
take pride in creating them with your own hands!
涙した過去への願いを
Turn your wishes for the tearful past
レクイエムにして
into a requiem.
聖なる全知全能の力で
With holy, omnipotent power,
この灼熱 Future
illuminate this burning future
信じて照らせ
with belief!
星天ギャラクシィクロス
Seiten Galaxy Cross!
一人じゃないことを
So that one day you will know
やがて君は知る日のため
that you are not alone,
指先伝わる
conveyed through our fingertips,
分かち合って明日に向かう
we share and head towards tomorrow.
永遠なる空に
Into the eternal sky,
I feel you... 自由の魂は拘束させない
I feel you... free souls will never be bound.
不滅なる夢に
Into an immortal dream,
I feel you... 意志へと手を取り合え
I feel you... join hands towards that resolve!
運命も終局も
With the power to sever
断ち切る力で
both fate and the end!
煌めき
Glittering,
十字となって闇を暴く
it becomes a cross to expose the darkness.
駆け抜けた丘には
On the hill we ran through,
神様も知らない
a history unknown even to God
歴史が光り誇る
proudly shines with light.
舞い飛べ brave hearts
Fly high, brave hearts!
この絆
This bond,
星天ギャラクシィクロス
Seiten Galaxy Cross!
逆光のツバサで
With backlit wings,
Yes, just believe
不死なる炎で
With undying flames,
Ignition...!!
過去を背負い戦おう
Let's carry our past and fight!
事故・奇跡は待つものじゃなくて
And miracles aren't something to wait for,
その手で創るものと... 吼えろ！
but something to create with your own hands... Roar!
何度だって 何度だって 立ち上がろうか！
No matter how many times, let me stand up again!
生ある全のチカラで
With all the power of living existence,
輝け future world
shine, future world!
信じ照らせ
Believe and illuminate,
星天ギャラクシィクロス
Seiten Galaxy Cross!
3人 トリオ DREAM
3-person Trio DREAM!
Let's sing! Let's dance! Let's go! Let's smile! Let's fly!
(Uh... 3, 2, 1) Let's sing! Let's sing! Let's dance! Let's go! Let's smile! Let's fly!
出会いに惹かれ合って (未来)
Drawn together by our encounter (Future)
1 + 1 + 1 は (無限)
1 + 1 + 1 is (Infinite)
唇からこぼれる歌は
The song overflowing from our lips
(Lalalalu Lilala) トリズム 眩しい光
(Lalalalu Lilala) Trio rhythm, dazzling light
(騒がしい) 3人寄れば文殊も最高！
(Boisterous) Three minds gathered together are the best!
(最高！) 始まる歌 第1章
(The best!) The song begins, Chapter 1
(Now, relaxed, enjoy together) ハミング (Fuu!) ジャズロック (Fuu!) カンツォーネ (Fuu!) コーラス＆レスポンス
(Now, relaxed, enjoy together) Humming (Fuu!) Jazz rock (Fuu!) Canzone (Fuu!) Call & response
輝くメロディ いいよね 好きな 好きな
A shining melody is great, isn't it? Favorite, favorite
フレーズを五線譜に 夢を乗せて 君・あなたのもとへ
Phrases on the staff, carrying dreams to you and everyone
(今夜) もっともっと 輝き合えるね
(Tonight) We can shine together even more!
(In, Out, Up, Down!) ひとつのスクリーンに いつだって 笑顔映し合おう
(In, Out, Up, Down!) On a single screen, let's always mirror each other's smiles
(Promise!) 君がいるからパワー 生まれるよ 今日も
(Promise!) Because you are here, power is born again today!
3人 トリオ DREAM
3-person Trio DREAM!
Let's sing! Let's dance! Let's go! Let's smile! Let's fly!
(Uh... 3, 2, 1) Let's sing! Let's sing! Let's dance! Let's go! Let's smile! Let's fly!
一緒だから感じ合える (Happily)
Because we're together, we can feel it (Happily)
(One, Two, Three) 1 × 1 × 1 は (無敵)
(One, Two, Three) 1 × 1 × 1 is (Invincible)
出し惜しみは無しで 全部あげたい
Without holding anything back, I want to give it all to you
(Give you, To me, La-la-la) ハプニングさえも超えていく
(Give you, To me, La-la-la) Overcoming even unexpected happenings
(Wonderful!) 3人寄れば文殊の知恵
(Wonderful!) Three heads are better than one
(知恵！) 見せるよ きっと伝説のライブ アンコール必至！
(Wisdom!) We'll show you a legendary concert, an encore is guaranteed!
(Jump! Jump! La-la-la) イルミネーション (Fuu!) ポップコーン (Fuu!) シャンソン (Fuu!) All ya welcome!
(Jump! Jump! La-la-la) Illumination (Fuu!) Popcorn (Fuu!) Chanson (Fuu!) All ya welcome!
カテゴリーサイズ いらないね 好きだ 好きだ
No need for categorization or sizing! I love it, I love it
思い切り音符の 羽を広げ 心の奥の奥へ
Spread the wings of musical notes to the deepest depths of our hearts
(Fly High!) 気持ちは 輝きでできているの
(Fly High!) Our feelings are made of pure brilliance
(Up, Down!) ビッグスクリーンも はみだしちゃう 嬉しいや 楽しい
(Up, Down!) Overflowing even beyond the big screen, so happy and fun!
(One Plus!) 君を知って知らなかった 自分に会えたよ
(One Plus!) By knowing you, I met a self I never knew before
3人 トリオ DREAM
3-person Trio DREAM!
Let's sing! Let's sing! Let's dance! Let's go! Let's smile! Let's fly!
プリキュア！！！
Precure!!!
Let's sing! Let's sing! Let's dance! Let's go! Let's smile! Let's fly!
輝くメロディ いいよね 好きな 好きな
A shining melody is great, isn't it? Favorite, favorite
フレーズを五線譜に 夢を乗せて 君・あなたのもとへ
Phrases on the staff, carrying dreams to you and everyone
(For you!) もっともっと 輝き合えるね みんな
(For you!) We can shine together even more, everyone!
Get down!
瞳水晶に
On our crystal eyes,
いつまでも笑顔映し合おう
let's always reflect each other's smiles,
promise
キミがいるからパワー生まれるよ 今日も
Because you're here, power is born today, too!
Try try trio dreams
Let's sing Let's swing Let's dance Let's bound Let's smile Let's fly
Woo プリキュア！！！
Woo Precure!!!
Let's sing Let's swing Let's dance Let's bound Let's smile Let's fly
Awakening Harmony
[Title: Awakening Harmony]
暗闇の真ん中 まっすぐなまなざしで
In the middle of the darkness, with a straight gaze,
立ち上がる姿 ちゃんと見ていたよ
I was watching your standing figure properly.
閉じ込められそうな 心を奮い立たせ
Rousing my heart that seemed to be trapped,
おさまりきらない 輝きを放ち
unleashing a brilliance that cannot be contained.
射抜かれた胸の奥 焼きついた眩しさは
Pierced deep inside my chest, the burned-in dazzling light...
それだけでもう 理由になる
that alone is already reason enough.
待っていて 取り戻したい 光の世界
Wait for me, I want to take back the world of light.
その笑顔 勇気 涙 夢
That smile, that courage, those tears, those dreams,
希望の兆し
the first signs of hope.
キミと明日を願う力で
With the strength to wish for tomorrow with you,
生まれるわたしたちのハーモニー
our harmony is born.
響け
Resound!
それでも暗闇は 訪れてしまうもの
Even so, darkness is something that will visit.
惑わされないで キミはキミだから
Don't be misled, because you are you.
渡しあえた日々が ハートを輝かせる
The days we shared make our hearts shine,
ひとりじゃないこと 気づかせてくれる
making us realize we are not alone.
抱えきれないほどの ありがとうの代わりに
In place of a thank-you too overwhelming to hold,
鍵をかけて ひとつになる 受け止めて
lock it up, become one, and accept it.
取り戻すんだ 光の未来
We will take back the future of light.
今 熱い想い繋ぐ声
Now, the voices connecting passionate feelings...
叶えに行くよ
we're going to make it come true!
君と一緒に願える奇跡
The miracles we can wish for together with you,
重ねて広かっていくハーモニー
a harmony that overlaps and continues to spread.
目覚める時が来たね
The time to awaken has come, hasn't it?
ホントの自分になる
We become our true selves.
満ちる運命
A fulfilling destiny.
取り戻したい 光の世界
I want to take back the world of light.
その笑顔 勇気 涙 夢
That smile, that courage, those tears, those dreams,
希望の兆し
the first signs of hope.
キミと明日を願う力で
With the strength to wish for tomorrow with you,
生まれるわたしたちのハーモニー
our harmony is born.
響け
Resound!
トライアングル・ドリーマー
[Title: Triangle Dreamer]
day by day 日に日に募るの乙女心
Day by day, a maiden's feelings grow stronger day by day.
同じクラス
In the same class,
斜め前のおとなしい人
sitting diagonally ahead of me, a quiet guy.
カッコ良くはないけど
He's not particularly cool,
優しい
but he's kind.
いつも頼れる彼
A guy I can always rely on.
アフタースクール 恋愛相談の帰り道
After school, on the way home after love advice,
なんだって話せる親友の女の子
a female best friend I can talk to about anything.
スポーツ万能 勉強もできて 女子力マックスです
Great at sports, good at studying, with maximum girliness.
どこにでもある
It happens everywhere,
よくあること
a very common thing.
急に彼女が
Suddenly, she said,
「あのね、実は私好きな人がいるの…！」って
"You know, I actually have someone I like...!"
ちょ、マジで！？
Wait, seriously!?
三角形 三角形の恋は気まぐれ
Triangle, triangular love is so fickle.
一瞬で 一瞬で崩れるバランス
In an instant, in an instant, the balance falls apart.
ベタなマンガみたいなフラグ
A classic manga-like flag.
まさかね自分が立てちゃうなんて残念すぎます！
Never thought I'd raise it myself, it's so sad!
三角形 三角形の恋は不安定
Triangle, triangular love is unstable.
なんちゃって なんちゃっちゃじゃ済まないカテゴリー
A category where 'just kidding' won't cut it.
恋と友情 ゆらゆらめいて
Love and friendship wavering back and forth.
なんか青春しちゃいます
I feel like I'm experiencing youth.
わたし困っちゃいます
I'm in a real fix.
完敗です！お似合いすぎるわ 勝手っこない
Total defeat! You two are too perfect together, I stand no chance.
悔しいけどとかそんなんじゃなくて本心
It's not that I'm bitter, this is my true feeling.
てゆーかすでに応援モード
Or rather, I'm already in support mode.
むしろ清々しい
In fact, it feels refreshing.
だけど彼女は
But she has...
不思議な顔
...a strange look on her face.
真剣な目で
With serious eyes, she says,
「そうじゃなくて、私あなたが好き…ゴメン」って
"Not him, I like you... I'm sorry."
ちょ、マジで！？
Wait, seriously!?
三角形 三角形の恋は気まぐれ
Triangle, triangular love is so fickle.
一瞬で 一瞬で崩れるバランス
In an instant, in an instant, the balance falls apart.
わたし アナタ 彼女とわたし
Me, you, her and me.
超絶！複雑！百合展開は想定外です！
Super complicated Yuri plot shift was completely unexpected!
三角形 三角形の恋は不安定
Triangle, triangular love is unstable.
なんちゃって なんちゃっちゃじゃ済まないカテゴリー
A category where 'just kidding' won't cut it.
解けないパズル与えたもうた
You bestowed an unsolvable puzzle upon me.
神よ恨んじゃいます
Oh God, I resent you for this.
わたし悩んじゃいます
I'm so troubled.
「あーっ！もう！スゴいヤバい！」
"Ah! Geez! This is so crazy!"
「好きだよ？好きだけど…って、そういう意味じゃなくって！」
"I like you, okay? I like you, but... wait, not in that way!"
「だって…女の子同士だし…」
"Because... we're both girls..."
「ねえ神様、どうしたらいいの？」
"Hey God, what should I do?"
「わたし、どうしたいの？」
"What do I even want to do?"
「ヘルプミ〜〜〜！！！」
"Help me~~~!!!"
なんか変だー 愛に国境も歳も性別もカンケーない！
Something's weird—love knows no borders, age, or gender!
けど、けど、けど！
But, but, but!
三角形 三角形の恋は気まぐれ
Triangle, triangular love is so fickle.
一瞬で 一瞬で崩れるバランス
In an instant, in an instant, the balance falls apart.
普通の恋 夢見てたのに
Even though I dreamed of a normal romance,
ノーマル設定のわたしじゃちょっと無理ゲーすぎます！
with my normal settings, this game is way too impossible!
三角形 三角形の恋は不安定
Triangle, triangular love is unstable.
なんちゃって なんちゃっちゃじゃ済まないカテゴリー
A category where 'just kidding' won't cut it.
彼女のこと好きになれたら
If I could actually fall in love with her,
なんて妄想しちゃいます
I catch myself fantasizing like that.
わたしどうかしてます
I must be going crazy.
PHOENIX PRAYER
劫々と続くショートショート
An eternally continuing short story
喪失は絶対零度だ
Loss feels like absolute zero
今夜はリィンカーネーション
Tonight is reincarnation
哀しみが混沌の子守唄歌ってるよ
Sadness is singing a lullaby of chaos
運命に理由があるのならば
If there is a reason to destiny,
すべてを賭けてみたいの
I want to gamble everything on it
あなたを守りたい
I want to protect you
どこまでも高く飛べるわ
I can fly endlessly high
どこまでも強く強くなれるわ
I can become infinitely stronger
信じて わたしに出会えたキセキ
Believe in the miracle of us meeting
切り開くは、不死鳥の炎
Carving a path forward with the phoenix's flame
説いて あなたのドグマ
Explain your dogma to me
blackout blackout 眼差しに泣きたくなるの
Blackout, blackout, your gaze makes me want to cry
flashback flashback 振りほどけ ascend
Flashback, flashback, break free and ascend
挑み続けろ
Keep on challenging
飄々と佇むホット・ショット
Standing nonchalantly like a hotshot
わたしが必要でしょ？
You need me, don't you?
今夜はリィンカーネーション
Tonight is reincarnation
正しさがストレイシープ最前線に押し出すよ
Righteousness pushes stray sheep to the front lines
運命に理由があるのならば
If there is a reason to destiny,
優しい世界をあげたい
I want to give you a gentle world
あなたを包むわ
I will enfold you
どこまでも速く射抜くわ
I'll pierce through with speed, wherever it leads
どこまでも熱く熱く焦がすわ
I'll scorch with passion, wherever it leads
信じて わたしに出会えたキセキ
Believe in the miracle of us meeting
切り開くは、不死鳥の炎
Carving a path forward with the phoenix's flame
説いて あなたのドグマ
Explain your dogma to me
blackout blackout 肩越しに光を見せて
Blackout, blackout, show me light over your shoulder
flashback flashback 許さない betray
Flashback, flashback, I won't forgive betrayal
進み続けろ 尽きるまで
Keep moving forward until the very end
傍にいると 鼓動が速くて 目眩がする
When I'm beside you, my heart beats fast and I feel dizzy
全て捧げる もう決めたの
I'll devote everything, I've already decided
最後のチャンスだからもう離さない
This is the last chance, so I won't let go
灼に燃ゆる未来の風に跨っていけ
Ride upon the wind of the brightly burning future
どこまでも高く飛べるわ
I can fly endlessly high
どこまでも強く強くなれるわ
I can become infinitely stronger
信じて わたしに出会えたキセキ
Believe in the miracle of us meeting
闇夜も望めば赫夜にするから
If you desire it, I'll turn even the dark night into bright red
切り開くは、不死鳥の炎
Carving a path forward with the phoenix's flame
説いて あなたのドグマ
Explain your dogma to me
blackout blackout 眼差しに泣きたくなるの
Blackout, blackout, your gaze makes me want to cry
flashback flashback 振りほどけ ascend
Flashback, flashback, break free and ascend
挑み続けろ
Keep on challenging
blackout blackout 肩越しに光を見せて
Blackout, blackout, show me light over your shoulder
flashback flashback 許さない betray
Flashback, flashback, I won't forgive betrayal
進み続けろ
Keep moving forward
神様に 恋をしてた頃は
Back when I was in love with God,
こんな別れが 来るとは思ってなかったよ
I never thought a parting like this would come.
もう二度と 触れられないなら
If I can never touch you again,
せめて最後に
then at least at the end...
もう一度抱きしめて欲しかったよ
I wanted you to hold me one last time.
It's long long good-bye...
さよなら さよなら
Goodbye, goodbye,
何度だって
no matter how many times,
自分に 無情に
relentlessly to myself,
言い聞かせて
I tell myself.
手を振るの は優しさだよね?
Waving goodbye is kindness, right?
今 強さが欲しい
Right now, I want strength.
貴方に出逢い STAR輝いて
Meeting you, the star shone,
アタシが生まれて
and I was born.
愛すればこそ iあればこそ
Because I love, because I am here,
希望のない 奇跡を待って
waiting for a hopeless miracle...
どうなるの?
What will become of me?
涙に滲む 惑星の瞬きは gone...
The twinkling of stars blurred by tears is gone...
忘れないよ 貴方の温もりも
I won't forget your warmth,
その優しさも
nor your gentleness,
全て包んでくれた両手も
nor your hands that embraced everything.
It's long long good-bye...
さよなら さよなら
Goodbye, goodbye,
愛しい人
my beloved.
貴方が いたから
Because you were there,
歩いてこられた
I was able to keep walking.
ひとりなんかじゃなかったよね?
I wasn't alone, right?
今 答えが欲しい
Right now, I want an answer.
燃える様な流星 捕まえて
Catching a burning meteor,
火を灯して
light a fire with it.
愛していたい 愛されていたい
I want to love, I want to be loved.
冷えたカラダひとつで
With just this cold body,
世界は どうなるの?
what will become of the world?
張り続けてた 虚勢が溶けてく long for...
The bravado I kept holding onto melts away, longing for...
どうしてなの?
Why is this happening?
涙溢れて
My tears overflow...
止められない
and I can't stop them.
貴方に出逢い STAR輝いて
Meeting you, the star shone,
アタシが生まれて
and I was born.
愛すればこそ iあればこそ
Because I love, because I am here,
希望のない 奇跡を待って
waiting for a hopeless miracle...
どうなるの?
What will become of me?
涙に滲む 惑星の瞬きは...
The twinkling of stars blurred by tears...
もし生まれ変わって また巡り会えるなら
If we are reborn and happen to meet again,
その時もきっと
then at that time too,
アタシを見つけ出して
please find me.
もう二度と離さないで
Never let go of me again,
捕まえてて
hold on to me.
ひとりじゃないと
That I am not alone,
ささやいてほしい planet...
I wish you would whisper, planet...
聖なる瞳が
If your sacred eyes
痛みを映したら
reflect pain,
振り向いてご覧?
won't you turn around and look?
情熱放つ Trick
It's a trick releasing passion.
崩れる足元
With the ground crumbling beneath us,
二人は戻れない
the two of us cannot turn back.
差し伸べた手をほどかないで
Don't let go of the hand I reached out to you.
消えるよまた 優しい日々が
Once again, those gentle days disappear,
思い出を汚すのは 許せない
and I won't allow our memories to be stained.
ここは裏切りの楽園
This is a paradise of betrayal,
さ迷う心の果てに
at the edge of a wandering heart.
光を求めて 祈る言葉届けあなたに
Seeking light, may my prayer reach you.
囚われの羽が 遥かな空へと向かう
These imprisoned wings head toward the distant sky.
信じたいよ 私たち 孤独じゃない
I want to believe that we are not alone.
分かり合う
Understanding each other,
絆の中 離さない
within our bond, I won't let go.
始まる Destiny
Our destiny begins.
新たな願いに 鎖ほどける時
When the chains unravel for a new wish,
休ませてくれる? 深い眠りに
will you let me rest in a deep sleep?
わずかな希望が 私を強くする
A faint glimmer of hope makes me stronger,
ぬくもりに触れてみたいから
because I want to feel your warmth.
甦れば 儚いいのち
If resurrected, a fleeting life—
繰り返す愛しさが導いた
repeating affection has guided us.
胸に泡沫の調べ 流れる世界の終わり
A fleeting melody in my heart at the end of a flowing world.
諦めはしない 今が繋ぐ明日探そう
I won't give up; let's search for the tomorrow connected to now.
ちぎれ舞う羽は 未来の空にも向かう
Wings torn and fluttering head toward the sky of the future.
忘れないで 私たち ひとつの水晶
Don't forget that we are a single crystal.
輝いて
Shining brightly,
割れないのよ
we won't shatter.
離さない
I won't let go,
誓いの Destiny
of our sworn destiny.
Lost the paradise
消えるよまた 優しい日々が
Once again, those gentle days disappear,
思い出を汚すのは 許せない
and I won't allow our memories to be stained.
ここは裏切りの楽園
This is a paradise of betrayal,
さ迷う心の果てに
at the edge of a wandering heart.
光を求めて 祈る言葉届けあなたに
Seeking light, may my prayer reach you.
囚われの羽が 遥かな空へと向かう
These imprisoned wings head toward the distant sky.
信じたいよ 私たち 孤独じゃない
I want to believe that we are not alone.
分かり合う
Understanding each other,
絆の中
within our bond.
離さない
I won't let go...
見つめて Paradise Lost
Gazing at Paradise Lost...
Woah-oh-oh
やっとみんな会えたね
We've finally met, everyone!
Don't stop! No, don't stop 'til finish!!
高鳴った 全力走りたい
My heart's pounding, I want to run with all my might!
芝と砂とキミの追い切りメニュー
Turf, dirt, and your final training plan!
Turn up!
声出せ 叫べ
Raise your voice, shout it out!
Woah-oh-oh
トレセン！ファイ！ (オー！) ファイ！ (オー！)
Tracen! Fight! (Oh!) Fight! (Oh!)
高鳴った 全力上がりタイム
My heart's pounding, full-speed final stretch time!
譲れない夢の途中
On the way to an unyielding dream,
Wow wow
走れよ ここから最高 story
Run! From here starts the ultimate story!
Woah-oh-oh-oh
あこがれの地へ (勇気少し借りて)
To the land of my dreams (borrowing a little courage),
語り合った memory (二度と来ない今を)
the memories we shared (living this moment that won't come again).
もう ドキドキも トキメキも
Now, neither the pounding nor the fluttering in my heart
抑えられない たまんない
can be held back, it's irresistible!
熱いハラハラが止まらない
This burning thrill won't stop!
キミと
With you,
走り競いゴール目指し
racing each other toward the finish line,
遥か響け届け music
let the music echo far and wide!
ずっとずっとずっとずっと 想い夢がきっとかなうなら
Forever and ever, if our cherished dreams will surely come true...
あの日 キミ に 感じた なにか を 信じて
Believing in that special something I felt in you that day,
春 も 夏 も 秋 も 冬 も 超え 願いあこがれ 走れ
surpassing spring, summer, autumn, and winter, run with your longing wishes!
Ah 勝利へ
Ah, toward victory!
Don't stop! No, don't stop 'til finish!!
Woah-oh-oh
高鳴った 全力弾けたい
My heart's pounding, I want to burst with all my might!
期待出会い決意絆になった
Expectations, encounters, and resolve became our bond!
Hands up!
本気で叫べ
Shout with all your heart!
Woah-oh-oh
トレセン！ファイ！ (オー！) ファイ！ (オー！)
Tracen! Fight! (Oh!) Fight! (Oh!)
高鳴った 全力笑いたい
My heart's pounding, I want to smile with all my might!
ターフのど真ん中
Right in the middle of the turf!
Wow wow
リアルに ここから上昇 story
For real, an ascending story starts right here!
Woah-oh-oh-oh
駆け抜けた日々 (昨日よりも今日を)
Days we ran through (focusing on today rather than yesterday),
語り合った glory (強くなれる理由)
the glory we talked about (the reason we can grow stronger).
今 応えたい "生きてる" と
Right now, I want to prove that "I'm alive"!
背中押す声 熱くなる
The voices pushing me forward burn hot!
夢は夢のまま 終われない
A dream cannot end as just a dream!
キミと
With you,
未来描きゴール目指し
drawing the future, aiming for the finish line,
狙え挑め掴め winning
aim, challenge, seize the victory!
ずっとずっとずっとずっと 想い夢はきっとかなうなら
Forever and ever, if our cherished dreams will surely come true...
あの日のキミが流した 涙も信じて
Believing even in the tears you shed that day,
雨も風も雲も闇も 超え願いあこがれ 走れ
surpassing rain, wind, clouds, and darkness, run with your longing wishes!
Ah 勝利へ
Ah, toward victory!
ゆるぎない覚悟決して
With unwavering resolve, never faltering,
ひとつひとつ共に綴る記録
recording each and every step together,
背中に迫る迷い振り払え
shake off the doubts creeping up behind you!
今の自分を追い越すだけ
Just overtake who you are right now!
勝ちたい 勝ちたい 勝ちたい キミと勝ちたい
I want to win, I want to win, I want to win, I want to win with you!
未来描きゴール目指し
Drawing the future, aiming for the finish line,
狙え挑め掴め winning
aim, challenge, seize the victory!
ずっとずっとずっとずっと 想い夢はきっとかなうから
Forever and ever, because our cherished dreams will surely come true,
あの日のキミが流した 涙も信じて
believing even in the tears you shed that day!
春も夏も秋も冬も超え
Surpassing spring, summer, autumn, and winter,
雨も風も雲も闇も超え 勝利へ
surpassing rain, wind, clouds, and darkness, toward victory!
キミと
With you,
走り競いゴール目指し
racing each other toward the finish line,
遥か響け届け music
let the music echo far and wide!
ずっとずっとずっとずっと 想い夢がきっとかなうなら
Forever and ever, if our cherished dreams will surely come true...
あの日 キミ に 感じた なにか を 信じて
Believing in that special something I felt in you that day!
夏も秋も冬も越え 願い焦がれ走れ
Crossing summer, autumn, and winter, run with burning desires!
ああ 勝利へ
Ah, towards victory!
未来描く軌道目指し 狙い定めつかめ Winning
Aiming for the trajectory toward the future, set your sights and grasp victory!
ずっとずっとずっとずっと思い 夢はきっと叶うから
Holding onto these feelings forever, because our dreams will surely come true!
あの日君が流した 涙も信じて
Believing even in the tears you shed that day...
雨も風も雲も闇も越え 願い焦がれ走れ
Crossing rain, wind, clouds, and darkness, run with burning desires!
ああ 勝利へ
Ah, towards victory!
Don't stop, Don't stop FINISH!
It's finally the true end
I'm ready for... my destiny
I'm ready for... STARTING OVER
やっと幕を下ろせた　最後の瞬間まで
I was finally able to lower the curtain... until the very last moment,
わたしは精一杯に　わたしをやりきった
I gave my absolute all to live as myself.
終演の続きは　誰も知らなくていい
No one needs to know what happens after the show ends,
涙を置いて　新しい旅に出よう
Let's leave our tears behind and set out on a new journey.
熱狂はあなたを選ぶ　違う結末だっただけ
Passion chooses you; it was simply a different outcome.
同じ愛になれなかった Destiny
A destiny that couldn't become the same love.
これまでの全てを　差し出すような愛だった
It was a love that offered up everything I had until now.
世界の意味が変わるくらいに　肯定された気がしたんだ
I felt validated, so much that it changed the meaning of the world.
何気なさの中で　気づけた最初の奇跡が
The very first miracle I noticed in the midst of ordinary life...
あなたでよかった　わたしでよかった　心から思えたよ
I truly felt from the bottom of my heart: I'm glad it was you, glad it was me.
ずっと遠い未来も　ちゃんと覚えていよう
Even in the far distant future, let's remember this well:
自分の抱きしめかた　明日の願いかた
How to embrace myself, how to wish for tomorrow.
あなたがいなくても　わたしの片隅で
Even if you're not here, in a corner of my heart,
優しい光　消えたりしないとわかる
I know that gentle light will never fade away.
今はまだ手を振れるほど　道は分かれたばかりで
Right now our paths have only just parted, not enough to wave goodbye yet,
後ろ髪に風を感じながら
Feeling the wind pull back against my hair...
それまでの全てが　あなたに出会うためだった
Everything up until then was all to meet you.
どの瞬間もムダじゃないこと　本当の意味で知れたから
Because I learned in the truest sense that no moment was in vain,
次の曲がり角も　自分らしさで選べるはず
I should be able to choose the next turn staying true to myself.
いつかに繋がる　新しい一歩　信じて歩き出そう
Believing in a new step leading to someday, let's start walking forward.
心から誰かを愛せた　あの日々は
Those days when I could love someone from my heart
間違いなくわたしの Destiny Ah,
Were unequivocally my destiny, ah...
これまでの全てが　新しい力をくれる
Everything up until now gives me new strength.
どの瞬間もムダじゃないなら　何が起きても大丈夫だから
If no moment was in vain, whatever happens will be alright.
次の物語も　自分らしさで選べるはず
I should be able to choose the next story staying true to myself.
いつかに繋がる　わたしのはじまり　信じて歩き出そう
Believing in my new beginning leading to someday, let's start walking forward.
いつかに繋がる わたしのはじまり 信じて歩き出そう
Let's believe in my new beginning, connected to someday, and step forward.
再び幕は上がる
Once again, the curtain rises.
聴いていただいたのは新曲の「STARTING OVER」でしたー！
That was my new song, "STARTING OVER"!
はい！新年一発目、新曲の初披露というわけで、ぬるっとね、新曲をやってしまったんですが...
Yes! As the very first song of the new year, it was a premiere performance of my new song... though I kind of slipped right into it...
平成感のある、えー、懐かしみの感じの楽曲を、こちらですね、歌わせていただいたんです...
I got to sing a song with a Heisei-era vibe and a sense of nostalgia...
...けれどーも！このあと、この曲が、えーっと、24時から...
...however! Right after this, starting from 24:00...
1月30日の24時から配信リリースされます！たくさん聴いてください！
On January 30th at midnight, it will be released digitally! Please listen to it a lot!
今年もね、たくさんオリ曲出していきたいです！
I want to release lots of original songs this year too!
そしてそして、もうMCがね、実は最後なのでね。
And also, this is actually the final talk segment.
えーっと、この配信のあとには、メンバー限定の配信もあるので、よろしくお願いします！
So after this stream, there'll be a members-only stream as well, so please stay tuned!
よし、よし、よし！グッズ紹介ー！
Alright, alright, alright! Merch introduction!
えー、ここには同期のねポラボを大集合ということで、ねー、らー、ぼー、集まれー！
Here we have a big gathering of my genmates, NePolabo! Nene, Lamy, Botan, assemble!
イエーイ！
Yay!
はい、ちゃっちゃっちゃっちゃー、初めて呼ばれました、どうも〜
Ta-da! We were called here for the first time, hello~
え？初だっけ？ポルカチャンネル初でーす！
Huh? Was this the first time? First time on Polka's channel!
誕生日おめでとうー！ありがとうー！
Happy birthday! Thank you~!
ここまでが流れでございます（笑）はい。
That was all scripted/according to plan (laughs). Yes.
グッズをね、紹介させていただきたいと思います！
I'd like to introduce the merchandise!
出演しながらね、リアクションなどを各々取っていただけたら嬉しいです！
I'd be happy if you all could react while participating!
尾丸ポルカ誕生日記念グッズ2026、ラインナップはこちら！
Omaru Polka Birthday Celebration Merch 2026, here is the lineup!
ドーン！というわけで、素晴らしい、今回もラインナップが揃っております！
Ta-da! So, we have an amazing lineup gathered once again!
え、なんか...あれ？すごいけど...あれ？ちょっとあれが...
Wait, something... Huh? It's awesome, but... Wait, isn't that a bit...?
ちょっと、なんか盛ってません？盛ってませんよ！
Wait, aren't you embellishing a bit? No, I'm not!
というわけで、まず一つ一つ紐解いていきましょう！
So let's look into each item one by one!
まずはこちら！はい！ポルカのはじめての抱き枕カバーとなっております！
First up, this! Yes! It's "Polka's First Body Pillow Cover"!
すごい！可愛い！え、ちょっとポルカさん、パンツ履いてません？
Amazing! Cute! Wait, Polka, aren't you not wearing pants?
あれ？丸出しじゃないですか？部屋着だよ〜！
Huh? Aren't you totally exposed? It's roomwear~!
部屋着？だってねねとかだってこういう部屋着...
Roomwear? But even Nene has roomwear like this...
待って待って、人のチャンネルだからってやりたい放題チャンネルして...
Wait, wait, just because it's someone else's channel, doing whatever you want...
写真撮影用かもしれないですよ！なるほどね。
Maybe it's for a photo shoot! I see.
というわけで、初めての抱き枕カバー出します。表が通常衣装で、裏は彼氏シャツになってます！
So, I'm releasing my first body pillow cover. The front is my normal outfit, and the back is a boyfriend shirt!
彼氏シャツいただきました！ありがとねー！
Boyfriend shirt acquired! Thank you~!
続きまして、ドン！こちら！歴代衣装のポルカ ランダムラバーストラップです！
Next up, boom! This! "Polka's Past Outfits Random Rubber Strap"!
これまでの衣装のラバーストラップ、こちら「いぬいみ」先生に書いていただきました！
Rubber straps of my past outfits, illustrated by Inuimi-sensei!
どの衣装が出るかお楽しみです。ありがとね、みんなリアクション本当に100点満点です！
Look forward to seeing which outfit you get! Thanks everyone, your reactions are 100 points!
はい、続きまして、こちらー！「どれもこれも宝物！思い出バインダー」！
Yes, next is this! "Each and Every One is a Treasure! Memory Binder"!
最近みんなも特典でチェキ風のブロマイドカード出したりしてるから、そういうの入れられたり...
Everyone's been releasing cheki-style bromide cards as bonuses lately, so you can put those in...
あとはホロカも入るサイズになっていますので、ぜひぜひいろんな思い出しまってください！
It's also sized to fit HoloCa cards, so please store all kinds of memories in it!
はい！そして続きましては、こちら！ポルカのしっぽキーホルダー！
Yes! And next is this! "Polka's Tail Keychain"!
一周して流行ってるからね！ポルカのしっぽ型のキーホルダーです！
It's coming back into trend after coming full circle! It's a keychain shaped like Polka's tail!
平成レトロみたいな感じでございます！こちらも付けてください！
It has a Heisei retro vibe! Please wear this too!
そしてボイスも出ます！ボイスはこちら、ジャーン！ASMRボイスです！
And we also have a voice pack! The voice pack is this, ta-da! An ASMR voice pack!
『彼シャツポルカの、ただいまの距離。』
"Boyfriend-Shirt Polka's 'I'm Home' Distance."
ちょっとタイトルもなんか狙ってる...エチコンの天下！やめてー！
The title is kinda deliberate... Erotic content dominance! Stop it~!
なんで今日同期呼んじゃったんだろうっていうのを一瞬思った、今恥ずかしくなってきた...
I suddenly wondered why I invited my genmates today, now I'm feeling embarrassed...
添い寝ASMRということで、抱き枕カバーとイラストの関係があるシナリオになってます！
It's a sleeping-together ASMR, with a scenario connected to the body pillow cover illustration!
そしてお待たせしました！フルセット購入特典になっております！こちら！チェキ風ブロマイドカード！
And thank you for waiting! Here is the full set purchase bonus! This cheki-style bromide card!
数量限定が直筆メッセージ、箔押し複製サインになっております！
The limited-quantity version comes with a handwritten message and foil-stamped duplicated signature!
通常が箔押し複製サインとメッセージ入りでございます！
The regular version includes a foil-stamped duplicated signature and message!
フルセットぜひぜひ買っていただいた方には、特典ボイスとして「すやすやポルカの、いちばん広い約束。」
For those who buy the full set, you get the bonus voice: "Sleeping Polka's Broadest Promise."
一緒にね、「寝ようね」みたいな感じの...
It's like, "Let me sleep with you," or something...
...ボイスになってて、こっちもASMRになってます。
...kind of voice pack, and this one is also ASMR.
おー！
Oooh!
よろしくお願いしますー！
Thank you so much!
恥ずかしいなぁ...みんなでやるの、これ。
This is so embarrassing... doing this all together.
なんか、えっちな女になっちゃって...
I feel like we've become naughty girls...
いいじゃない。
What's wrong with that?
今年もね、皆さん改めてこれからよろしくお願いします！
Once again, we look forward to your support this year as well!
よろしくお願いしまーす！
We look forward to it!
ということでね、今日はみんなで最後一緒に歌を歌うために呼んできたということで、準備してきまーす！
So today, I called everyone here so we can sing a final song together! We're gonna go get ready!
いってらっしゃーい！じゃあねー！
Off you go! See ya!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
脚本は捨てちゃおうか
Let's throw away the script!
さあしっかりと焼き付けよう！
Now, make sure to burn this into your memory!
アドリブの熱いパフォーマンス
This passionate, ad-libbed performance!
屋根裏を飛び出して
Bursting out of the attic,
壮大なステージに響く
echoing across this grand stage...
特別なストーリー
...is a special story.
瞼の裏には虹が紡ぐ
Behind our eyelids,
星空のメモリー
a memory of a starry sky woven with rainbows.
等身大の愛を込めて
Filled with our true, heartfelt love...
想像を超える世界へ
...to a world beyond imagination!
誰も知らないでしょ
Nobody knows yet, right?
Are you ready?
どんな未来か見に行こうよ
Let's go see what kind of future awaits!
なんて自由だ！笑っちゃうよね
It's so liberating, it makes me laugh!
ねえ ホログラムよりも先へ
Hey, let's go even further beyond holograms!
誰だって置いてかないよ
We won't leave anyone behind!
ごらん！歓声が呼んでいる
Look! The cheers are calling us!
スナップからパッと照らす
With a snap, lighting up
人生のスポットライト
life's spotlight in an instant!
薔薇色のプレミアショー
A rose-colored premiere show!
ここが特等席よ
This right here is the best seat!
本日ロマンス日和
Today is a perfect day for romance,
(天気次第のエチュード)
(An etude at the mercy of the weather)
まるで絵物語
Just like a picture book story.
捕まえてよ (待って)
Catch me! (Wait!)
ほら (待って)
Come on! (Wait!)
予想のできない展開に
At unexpected developments,
ステージは揺れる
the stage sways!
格別なストーリー
An extraordinary story.
耳を澄ましたら 月が踊る
If you listen closely, the moon dances,
雨粒のハーモニー
to the harmony of raindrops.
浮かぶ ふわふわな空想
Fluffy fantasies floating up,
暴走？底なしの本能！
Running wild? Endless instinct!
すべて知りたいでしょ
You want to know everything, don't you?
Hey guys! 叫べ気分は最高？
Hey guys! Shout out, feeling great?
最高！
The best!
Come on! もっと叫べ気分は最高？
Come on! Shout louder, feeling great?
最高！
The best!
ポルカ終わるか？
Is Polka gonna end?
終わらない！ It's showtime!
It's not over! It's showtime!
繋いだ手離さないでなんてね
"Don't let go of my hand," just kidding!
どうしたって重たくなっちゃって困るわ
Becoming overly needy would be a problem...
いつかの日かエピローグを一緒に綴ろう
Someday, let's write the epilogue together.
きっと約束よ Life goes on!
It's a promise, Life goes on!
どんな未来か見に行こうよ
Let's go see what kind of future awaits!
なんて自由だ！笑っちゃうよね
It's so liberating, it makes me laugh!
ねえ ホログラムよりも先へ
Hey, let's go even further beyond holograms!
夢のような花舞台に感情を馳せたら
Sending our feelings out onto this dreamlike grand stage...
スナップからパッと照らす
With a snap, lighting up
人生のスポットライト
life's spotlight in an instant!
薔薇色のプレミアショー
A rose-colored premiere show!
どこへだって添い遂げたい
I want to stay by your side wherever we go.
ここが特等席よ
This right here is the best seat!
あんたにゃ もったいない
I'm too good for you
あたしゃ ほんと NICE BODY BODY BODY
I really have a nice body, body, body
自分じゃ 浮くくらい
I feel so light, almost floating
タダじゃない じゃない
I don't come cheap, not cheap
熱けりゃ 冷ませばいい
If it's too hot, just cool it down
寂しけりゃ EVERYBODY BODY BODY
If you're lonely, everybody, body, body
誰にも 分からない
Nobody really knows
恋愛って いつ火がつくのか
When love will ignite
DYNAMITE
恋は DYNAMITE
Love is dynamite
どんなに 不景気だって 恋は インフレーション
No matter how bad the economy is, love is inflation
こんなに 優しくされちゃ ミドロ
When you're this gentle to me, I'm completely smitten
明るい未来に 就職希望だわ
I want to apply for a job in a bright future
日本の未来は
The future of Japan
世界がうらやむ
Is the envy of the world
恋をしようじゃないか
Why don't we fall in love?
Dance! DANCING ALL NIGHT
なんだか 物足りない
Somehow, it's just not enough
どこにいたって 愛しててほしいわ
Wherever I am, I want you to love me
自分で 伝えるの
Saying it myself
恥ずかしいじゃない
Isn't that embarrassing?
いっそ 踊ろう
Let's just dance instead
ふたりが WOW WOW
The two of us, wow wow
あこがれよ EVERYBODY BODY BODY
Long for it, everybody, body, body
誰もが 気づいてない
Nobody has noticed
恋愛って 夢の落とし穴
Love is a pitfall of dreams
MYSTERY
恋は MYSTERY
Love is a mystery
こんなの 不自然だって 恋のインサイダー
Even if this seems unnatural, an insider of love
それでも 超愛されちゃ ラーワーイ
Still, being loved so deeply makes me so happy
幸せ 来る日も キャンセル待ちの
Happiness, every coming day, is on the waiting list
あんたの笑顔は
Your smile
世界がうらやむ
Is the envy of the world
夢があるじゃないか
There's a dream in it, isn't there?
Dance! DANCING ALL NIGHT
Wake up!
LOVE LOVE LOVE MACHINE
LOVE LOVE LOVE STATION
LOVE LOVE LOVE FACTORY
LOVE LOVE LOVE IS A WONDERFUL
Love, love, love is wonderful
日本の未来は
The future of Japan
世界がうらやむ
Is the envy of the world
恋をしようじゃないか
Why don't we fall in love?
Dance! DANCING ALL NIGHT
モーニング娘。も
Even Morning Musume
あんたもあたしも
You and me both
みんな社長さんも
Everyone, even company presidents
Dance! DANCING ALL NIGHT
LOVE MACHINE
今日は主役だ！！ まだまだ かがやく場所へ つれていけ！！ I LOVE YOU ♡
[On-screen text: Today I'm the star!! Take me to even brighter places!! I LOVE YOU ♡]
新曲のお披露目あり！ Glitter Love
Unveiling a new song! Glitter Love
ホロメンゲスト 10名
10 Hololive member guests